Guide to the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61 Records, 1943-1990 AIS.1989.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61, I.
  - Cobra, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Trial Board, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Phone Numbers and Addresses (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - National Labor Relations Board Affadavits (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Truweld Grating, Litchfield, IL, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Truweld MSDS (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The HMO Alliance (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Truweld Grating Retirement Plan, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Truweld Benefits (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Allegheny County Job Training Program Letters, Notices, Labor Relations Board Subpoena Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Metscrap Communications, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
  - Packaging Communications, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
  - Mechling Communications, 1980-19983 (Box 20, Folder 18-22)
  - Truweld Communications, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 23-36)
  - DMEC Communications, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 37-53)
  - DMEC Communications, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
  - Mellon Stick-Up Subpoenas, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Political Letters and Information, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 750, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Articles (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Photographs, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Neville Township Commissioners, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Law Firms, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Kathy Van Natta (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Shasta Communications, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Local 61 Information, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - To Be Paid, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Plant Closing Legislation, 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Aliquippa, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Coraopolis Politics, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Shasta Communications, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Myron Joseph, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - LMP Communications, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Union/Mechling Communications, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Information, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Food Bank, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Phone List (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Workers Solidarity Alliance Report, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Neville's Ark Food Bank (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Articles and Newsletters (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Fliers (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - For PLEM Arbitration, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - To Arbitration by Review Board, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - For Pre Arbitration, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Grievances for Dan Cooper Arbitration, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Carpenter and Pipe Shops, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Grievance Withdrawl, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - First Group to be Arbitrated, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Arbitration Case: John Herr, Joe Kress and Vince Maggio, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Group to be Arbitrated, July 19, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - To Arbitrate, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Group to be Arbitrated, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Grievances for Review Board, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Grievances for Arbitration, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Grievance Cases Not to be Arbitrated, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Grievances for All Departments, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Arbitration Cases for Past Years (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Grievances, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Grievances for All Departments, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Grievance for Arbitration for Dan Cooper, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Grievance to be Arbitrated, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1971, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1963-1964, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Structural Shop and Mold Loft (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Picket Roster, September 1, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - By-Laws of IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Membership Cards [RESTRICTED] (Box 22, Item 1)
  - Membership Cards [RESTRICTED] (Box 23-24)
  - Libertarian Labor Review #2: A Journal of Anarcho-Syndicalist Ideas & Discussion, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Trusteeship, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Meatcutters P-9, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Prearbitration Grievances (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Labor Board Cases (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Calendar, October 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Articles and Newspaper Clippings (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Report of Terminations, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Arnold Williams and Bill Wagner, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Grievances 6058-6118, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Grievances 5700-5799, October 1979-June 1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Maintenance Department Wheel Arbitrator, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Grievances, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - By-Laws Committee (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Relationships By Objectives, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
  - Safety, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Private Negotiation Meetings, Bill Wagner, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Pre Arbitration Settlements, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Brennan v. Dravo, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - National Communications, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Communications, December 10, 1969-January 27, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Pre Arbitration Records, Bill Wagner, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pension File, 1960-1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Grand Ave. Corporation, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Retirement, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Dravo Layoffs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Grievance Investigation Binder (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Heavy Metals Plant Seniority Register, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Grievance Information (Box 26, Folder 10-13)
  - Ernie Truffa Vacation (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Grievances (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Contact Lists (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Investigations, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Dravo Grievance Investigations, 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Dravo Grievance Investigations, 1976-1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Transfer Request Certificates (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Arbitration Awards, Neville Island, 1944-1970 (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Grievances, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
  - Grievance Investigation, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Truffa Records (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Communications, October 26-November 23, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - LMP (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, April 9, 1980 (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, November 13, 1981 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, April 9, 1976 (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, January 14, 1977 (Box 28, Item 4)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61, November 17, 1978 (Box 28, Item 5)
  - Hourly Job Descriptions, 1947, undated (Box 28, Item 6-7)
  - Arbitration, 1944-1985 (Box 29)
  - Grievances, 1969-1980 (Box 30)
  - Record Book of Funeral Donations, 1966-1979 (Box 31, Item 1)
  - Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1-8)
  - Grievance and Arbitration Files (Box 31, Folder 9-48)
  - Internal Correspondence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Labor Reports, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Safety Reports and National Correspondence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Terminations, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Retirees Dinner, March 21, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1971-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Agreements between Dravo and IUMSWA Local 61, 1959-1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Specifications for Modular Trailer Housing at Allegheny County Jail, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with the Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local 27, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Charitable Contributions (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Dravo Grievances, 1981-1982 (Box 33)
  - Grievances, 1970s-1980s (Box 34)
  - Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley and Denominational Ministry Strategy, 1984-1987 (Box 35)
  - Family Relief Fund (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Future of Southwestern Pennsylvania: An Inquiry in Leadership (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Article regarding the Solberg Brothers (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Churches (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy Fliers (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Fighting Ministers Binder (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - David Rosenburg and the Allegheny Conference on Human Development (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Ballot for Unopposed Candidates, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - MEC Ballots (Box 36, Folder 11-12)
  - Shasta Ballot (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Main Ballots (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Truweld Ballots (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Packaging Ballots (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Election, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Darrell Becker Bible (Box 36, Item 1)
  - Shadyside Presbyterian Fliers and Publications, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Shasta Fliers and Publications, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jesse Jackson Clippings, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Research Fliers and Publications, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
  - Rev. Roth Clippings, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy Leaflets, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  - Prophet Ministry Fliers and Publications, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - DeBartolo Fliers and Publications, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley News Releases, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - MSGR. Rice Fliers and Publications, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Dravo Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
  - Heinz Fliers and Publications, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Support Letters, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Printed Matter, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Passavant, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - East Liberty Presbyterian Fliers and Publications, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Memorial Service, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Tri-State Fliers and Publications, 1983-1984 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - US Steel, USWA Local 2227, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - McGraw Edison Fliers and Publications, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - John Guest, St. Stephens, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Jim Dix, Fox Chapel Episcopal, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Episcopal Diocese, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Catholics, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Lutherans, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Pittsburgh Offensive, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Douglas Dunderdale, Eastminster, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - John Galloway, Fox Chapel Presbyterian, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - George Wirth, Sewickley Presbyterian, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Barton Leach, Third Presbyterian, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Jim Long, Beula, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Bruce Thielemann, First Presbyterian, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Lairo Steward, Westminster, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Bernie Johnson, Mt. Lebanon, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Bill Pickering, St. Paul's, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Harold Scott, Pittsburgh Theological Seminary, Presbyterian, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Leonard Koshinski, Holy Family, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Dan Sullivan, St. Paul's Monastery, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - George Werner, Trinity, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Alvin Berkun, Tree of Life, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Morris Landes, Adath Jeshurun, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Rabbinic Fellowship, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Mark Mahler, Temple Emmanuel, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Mike Gold, Beth El, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Evelynn Dansker, Temple Sinai, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Rabbi Weiss, Bnat Emunoh, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Fr. Lackner, St. Margarets, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - United Methodist, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Frank Matola, St. Catherines, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Richard Goss, Covenant Community Presbyterian, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Walter Jacob, Rodef Shalom, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous Church Correspondence (Box 37, Item 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1985 (Box 38)
  - Church Contacts (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - AAA (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Personal, 1979-1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Phone Campaign, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Communications with Other Locals, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Union, 1980-1985 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Communication, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Dravo, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Strike Bulletins, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sunday Picket Captains, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Articles and Fliers (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - National Rank and File Against Concession, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Dravo Corp. Job Descriptions, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 15-35)
  - An Evangelical Confession: Pittsburgh 1985 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Roster Meetings (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Amendments, Convention, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Company Cassassanta (Fines), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Darrell Becker, Personal, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Roberts Rules of Order (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws A & B, May 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Truweld Negotiations, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Lippard, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Executive and Members' Notes, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Shasta Lost Time (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - LMP Lost Time (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - AMP Lost Time (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Sign for Bank (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Bills, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Charges and Verdicts, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Election Appeals, Results and Trial Boards, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Stencils (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Mellon, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Old Appeals Proceedures (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Research Paper #3 regarding Mellon Bank (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 40, Folder 22-24)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 40, Folder 25-26)
  - Activist Organizations (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 40, Folder 28-29)
  - D. Douglas Roth, Darrell Becker, and David Soul v. Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 30-34)
  - Department of Labor Election and Trusteeship Report, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Briefs in Brock v. IUMSWA, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Item 1)
  - Batson Depositions, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Item 2-3)
  - Becker Depositions, 1987 (Box 41, Item 4)
  - TRO v. IAM Merger, 1987 (Box 41, Item 5)
  - Dravo, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Contract, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Copies, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Scabs (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Dravo Information, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Pensions, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Dravo, 1977-1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - DMEC Negotiations, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Dravo Injunction Papers, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Labor Agreement, 1968-1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Job Descriptions, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Go To Pay, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Proposals, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Shop Trouble, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Retirement Plan, May 25, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Job Descriptions, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Employee List, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Dravo v. IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Handwritten Notes (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Report of Terminations, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Negotiation Information (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Communications from Dravo (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Forms and Receipts (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Chippers and Burners, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Dravo, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 14-15)
  - Dravo Stockholders, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Robert Dickey (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Faught, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
  - Lisa L. Elias, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Dravo Corporation Annual Report, 1981-1984 (Box 42, Item 1-4)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, Dravo Corporation, December 31, 1984 (Box 42, Item 5)
  - Dravo Retirement Plan, Summary Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Item 6)
  - Dravo Group Insurance Plan, Summary Annual Report, 1977 (Box 42, Item 7)
  - Agreement between Dravo Engineering Works and IUMSWA Local 61, 1980 (Box 42, Item 8)
  - Heavy Metals Plant Seniority Register, 1980 (Box 42, Item 9)
  - Dravo Retirement Plan, 1965 (Box 42, Item 10)
  - Welcome to the Senate of Pennsylvania (Box 42, Item 11)
  - Dravo Review, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Item 12-13)
  - Will You Get Caught in the Pension Trap?, 1982 (Box 42, Item 14)
  - Often-Asked Questions About the Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1974 (Box 42, Item 15)
  - Dravo Directory (Box 42, Item 16)
  - Blue Cross Coverage: A Handbook for Active Employees and Eligible Retirees of Dravo Corporation and Subsidiaries, 1981 (Box 42, Item 17)
  - Dravo Group Insurance Program, 1974 (Box 42, Item 18)
  - Workplace Exposure to Asbestos by National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, 1980 (Box 42, Item 19)
  - Dravo Annual Benefits Statement, 1982 (Box 42, Item 20)
  - Longshoremen, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Joe Pass, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Election Notes (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Communications, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 6-8)
  - Threats to Darrell Becker (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Blank Forms (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Family Relief, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Churches (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Addressed Envelopes (Box 43, Folder 14-17)
  - Glossary of Useful Labor Relations Terms (Box 43, Item 1)
  - List of Relevant Publications with Social and Economic Conditions of the Pittsburgh Region (Box 43, Item 2)
  - Pennsylvania Commodity Calendar, 1986 (Box 43, Item 3)
  - Darrell Becker Daily Planner, 1985 (Box 43, Item 4)
  - Extra Copies, 1985 (Box 43, Item 5)
  - Local 61 IUMSWA et al v. Arthur E. Baston and IUMSWA, 1988 (Box 43, Item 6)
  - Ann McLaughlin, Secretary of Labor v. IUMSWA, 1988 (Box 43, Item 7)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 44)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy and Mellon Bank (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 Steel Scrap Monument (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy Research (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Shadyside Presbyterian (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy Circulars (Box 45, Folder 8-9)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Denominational Ministry Strategy Fliers (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence regarding Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Church Information regarding Denominational Ministry Strategy (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Dravo, 1977-1982 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Retirement Plans, May 1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Church (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Trinity, 1983-1985 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Darrell Becker Prison Correspondence, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Church and Denominational Ministry Strategy Fliers (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Legal Papers (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America 42nd Convention Proceedings, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - IUMSWA Merger Information (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Harpoon Issue and IUMSWA Backlash, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Expenses, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - National Exposure, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Convention Notes and Appeals, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Sample Mailings (Box 46, Folder 9-12)
  - The Unifier, December 7, 1985 (Box 46, Item 1)
  - Correspondence and Papers Marked "Originals" (Box 46, Item 2-4)
  - IUMSWA Amendments, 1972-1982 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Appeals to Appeals Committee at Convention, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Donations and Support Letters, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Department of Labor Trusteeship, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Election, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - IUMSWA Charges v. Becker and Local 61, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - David Soul Events, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Convention Receipts (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - IUMSWA (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - MW of Pittsburgh, Packaging and Mets., 1988 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Metallurgical Exoproducts Corporation, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Shasta (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Local 61, Neville Island Member List (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Nicaragua (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Unity Party Slate, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Local 61 Independence and IUMSWA Resignations, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Activist Organizations (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - IUMSWA Local 61 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Darrell Becker (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Becker v. Baston, 1986 (Box 47, Item 1)
  - Becker Campaign (Box 47, Item 2)
  - Irregularities and Violations: IUMSWA Summary of Charges (Box 47, Item 3)
  - Activity Reports, Ted Pallas to IUMSWA Vice President Robert Pemberton, 1984-1987 (Box 47, Item 4)
  - Constitution of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (Box 47, Item 5)
  - IUMSWA Local 6 v. Batson, 1988 (Box 47, Item 6)
  - Paynter PTA Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Item 7)
  - Dues Card Receipts, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Ernie Soderst, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Beach, August 1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Temporary Assistance Arbitration, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dravo Grievances, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - NLRB Recertification Votes, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Secede, September 1984 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - $1000 Cancel Vouchers, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Paycheck Voucher and Financial Statements (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Assessments, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Strike Fund, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Batson Case to Appeal Committee, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Food Bank Minutes, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Shasta Meetings, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Shasta Negotiations, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Shasta, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Shasta Negotiations, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Contract Proposals, 1984-1987 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Shasta Grievances, 1981-1984 (Box 48, Folder 20-22)
  - Shasta Grievances, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Shasta (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Shasta Material Safety Data Sheets, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Beaver Valley Federal Credit Union (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1980-1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Shasta Negotiation Notes, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Shasta Negotiations, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Agreements between Shasta and Local 61, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8-18)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence and Grievances, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Shasta Inspection Manual, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Greg Brehm Inspector's Sheets, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Shasta Contracts, 1981-1990 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Shasta Correspondence and Grievances, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Shasta Grievances, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Contract Proposals between Shasta and IUMSWA, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Shasta (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Mail, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Affadavits v. Shasta, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Shasta Arbitration, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - S&S Grinders, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - MEC Negotiations, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Local 61 v. IUMSWA Injunction Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Shasta IAM Copies (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Communications, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Jeff Coffman, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Shasta, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)